<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Andrew Schllenberg</title><link>schellenberg.3.github.io/</link><description>Recent content on Andrew Schllenberg</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2023 Andrew Schellenberg</copyright><lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 09:18:26 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="schellenberg.3.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Hello!</title><link>schellenberg.3.github.io/blog/hello/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 Nov 2023 09:18:26 -0500</pubDate><guid>schellenberg.3.github.io/blog/hello/</guid><description>Thank you for checking out my website.
I am a C++ and Python developer doing applied research in robotics. How computers interact, observe, and represent the physical world fascinates me. My work intersects with machine vision, computational geometry, controls, and more.
There exists a near-infinite number of programming blogs. Hopefully, these ideas will inspire others working at the intersection of robotics and computer vision. It is not my intent to add noise or repeat hello world examples.</description></item><item><title>CV</title><link>schellenberg.3.github.io/cv/</link><pubDate>Mon, 27 Nov 2023 21:28:35 -0500</pubDate><guid>schellenberg.3.github.io/cv/</guid><description>Thank you for taking an interest in my skills. This page lists a brief summary of my education, work, and project experiences. For a more complete overview, you can download my full resume here.
Skills# Programing Languages (including common libraries)
C++, Python, CUDA, Eigen, OpenCV, Open3D, VTK &amp; ParaView, PyTorch &amp; LibTorch, TensorFlow Robotics and Autonomous Systems (focused in computer vision)
Linus, ROS2, Docker, Arduino, Raspberry PI Mechanical Design (focused in kinematics and controls)</description></item><item><title>About</title><link>schellenberg.3.github.io/about/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>schellenberg.3.github.io/about/</guid><description>Hi, I&amp;rsquo;m Andrew# I am a robotics researcher specializing in computer vision and autonomous systems. Environmental perception is foundational for decision-making in complex environments: my work develops novel approaches to solve mapping problems and generate digital twins of real-world locations and objects.
I believe in developing simple, elegant solutions to practical problems. Above all, I strive to make technology that is useful and accessible. I am a proponent of open-source technology; you may find much of my work on GitHub.</description></item></channel></rss>